in previous lectures we have seen you
在之前的课程中，我们见过你
can group elements by selecting them and
可以通过选择元素和对元素进行分组
choose group you can move and scale a
选择您可以移动和缩放的组
group like it is one object
像一个对象一样的群
we have also seen you can merge objects
我们还看到您可以合并对象
together using the union operation
一起使用联合操作
although the union operation is
尽管联合行动是
destructive when paths overlap this is
当路径重叠时这是破坏性的
normally what you want as we see after
通常情况下，您想要的是我们之后看到的
the union operation the original circles
工会在原有圈子里运作
are gone
都消失了
but there also is a non-destructive way
但还有一种非破坏性的方法
of merging overlapping paths called the
合并重叠路径，称为
compound path
复合路径
I select these two circles
我选择了这两个圆圈
to make them a compound path I go to
让它们成为我要去的一条复合道路
path combine in the layers panel we see
路径组合在我们看到的层面板中
we have merged two paths into a single
我们已将两条路径合并为一条
path
路径
but when I click on the Node tool I see
但当我单击节点工具时，我看到
I still have the two original circles I
我仍然保留着我原来的两个圆圈
select a circle by selecting its nodes
通过选择圆的节点来选择圆
to do this I hold my mouse above one of
为此，我将鼠标放在其中一个上方
the nodes which then becomes red then I
然后变成红色的节点，然后我
hold down control and scroll forward
按住Ctrl键并向前滚动
until all nodes are selected
直到选择了所有节点
I can now move the circle if I click on
我现在可以移动圆圈，如果我点击
the show transformation handles icon the
显示转换处理图标
circle can also be scaled I press the
圆圈也可以缩放。我按下
space bar to go to the select tool sew
按空格键可转到选择工具缝合
the compound path gives non-destructive
复合路径提供了非破坏性
results but its real power is that it
结果，但它的真正力量是它
can create holes in shapes I duplicate a
可以在我复制的形状中创建孔
circle and make it smaller I want the
圈起来，把它变小，我想要
orange circle to punch a hole in the
橙色圆圈，在
green circle because the circles don't
绿色圆圈，因为圆圈不是
overlap there is no danger of losing
重叠，不会有丢失的危险
geometry so I don't have to use combine
几何学，这样我就不必使用组合
with both circles selected I go to path
选择两个圆后，我将转到路径
difference when I click on the Node tool
当我单击节点工具时的差异
I see I still have the two paths I hold
我明白了，我还有两条我坚持的路
my mouse above a note of the inner
我的鼠标在里面的音符上面
circle press Ctrl and scroll forward
按Ctrl圈并向前滚动
until all nodes are selected we see I'm
直到所有节点都被选中，我们才能看到
able to move and scale the Inner Circle
能够移动和缩放内圈
so why does the Inner Circle create a
那么，为什么核心圈子会创造一个
hole with this circle we can see the
用这个圆圈我们可以看到
path Direction I duplicate it and make
路径方向我复制它并制作
it smaller I go to path difference
它变小了，我去了路径差
inkscape like illustrator will reverse
Inkscape Like Illustrator将反转
the path Direction which creates the
创建的路径方向
hole if I select the Inner Path and go
如果我选择内路径并开始
to path reverse the Inner Circle doesn't
要反转内圆的路径不
create a hole anymore because both paths
再创建一个洞，因为这两条路径
now go in the same direction I reverse
现在朝我倒车的方向走
the path again and I have a hole this
再走一次小路，我有一个洞
knowledge can be especially useful when
在以下情况下，知识可能特别有用
handling text this text is a single path
处理文本此文本是单个路径
so a compound path if I want to
所以，如果我想的话，这是一条复合路径
manipulate the letters individually I
逐个处理字母I
can go to path break apart
可以去小路分开
we see however with this operation we
然而，我们看到，通过这次行动，我们
lost the holes in the letters to get
丢了字母上的洞才能拿到
single letters without this problem I go
没有这个问题的单字母我走了
to path split path
路径拆分路径的步骤
now I have individual letters and the
现在我有了个人信件和
holes are retained I have encountered
我遇到过的洞被保留了下来
this problem in the past when opening
这个问题在过去打开的时候
PDFs containing text in illustrator
在Illustrator中包含文本的PDF
to make the letter e a compound path
要使字母e成为复合路径，请执行以下操作
again I make sure the larger part is
我再一次确保更大的部分是
placed behind the cutout path
放置在裁切路径后面
then I select both paths
然后我选择两条路径
I go to path difference I will do the
我去路径差异，我会做的
same for the O if you still not get the
如果你仍然没有得到O也是如此
hole which I haven't counted in the past
我以前没算过的洞
select the Inner Circle
选择内圆
then go to path reverse
然后转到路径反转
foreign
国外